Memorabilia Collection, 1782-2011 (bulk 1866-1997): Finding Aid AC053
University Archives
Memorabilia Collection
1775-2010
1866-1997
University Archives
Princeton University. Library. Department of Rare Books and Special Collections
Princeton University. Library. Special Collections
AC053
191 boxes
47 items
This collection contains over 1,800 items including mugs, pipes, canes, banners, hatbands, pins, jewelry, and other material collected by many individuals that document reunions, sporting events, student traditions, and other aspects of University life.
Scope and Contents
The clothing group includes handkerchiefs, hatbands, and neckties. Dishware includes plates, mugs, beer cans, and bottles, as well as ashtrays, cigarette cases, and class day pipes. The grounds and building memorabilia contains pieces of buildings, keys, and bells. (Some of the larger silver cups listed on the item list are stored in the vault. These are designated with a V in the box category.) The Medals series contains medals. The Pins series consists of patches, and pins, ribbons. The Stamps Series includes stamps, pins, a plaque, and an umbrella. The Miscellaneous series includes jewelry, canes and fans. (Some of memorabilia items are on permanent display at Mudd Library and the location of these is noted in the box category.) Some items are stored in a box from a different series simply because of size limitations. For instance, a metal tobacco sign is stored in the Sports series, Sports, simply because it did not fit in any of the tobacco boxes.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged by broad category as follows: 250th Anniversary; Awards; Clothing; Dishware; Grounds and Buildings; Banners and Pennants; Embossers; Medals; Miscellaneous; Pins and Ribbons; Sports; Stamps; and Tobacco Within each grouping, materials are arranged by type of item, for the most part. For example, all mugs are placed together within the Dishware group.
Conditions Governing Access
Collection is open for research use.
Other Finding Aids
In addition to these two lists, the information is contained in a database which can be keyword searched: Princeton Memorabilia Collection.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The collection was donated by hundreds of individuals over the course of several decades and continues to grow each year as additional items are received. Many individual items are marked with accession numbers which provide donor information..
Appraisal
No appraisal information is available.
College students -- New Jersey -- Princeton -- Societies and clubs.; Princeton (N.J.) -- Social life and customs.; Collectibles.; Ephemera.; Memorabilia.; Princeton university
- Series 1: 250th Anniversary, 1996-1997; 10 boxes
  Conditions Governing Access
  Collection is open for research use.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains memorabilia related to Princeton University's 250th Anniversary celebration.
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically.
  - Bronze medal, 1996; 1 box (Box F.3)
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    AR.1997.067
    with Palmer Stadium.
  - Folder, 1996; 1 box (Box F.2)
    AR.1996.097
    Blue folder of US Postal post card for Alexander Hall. "US Postal Service Princeton University US Postal Card Sept 20, 1996
  - Large bowl, 1996; 1 box (Box F.4)
    AR.2003.034
    Large commemorative bowl with Princeton shield at bottom. Orange and gold trim with pictures of important buildings on campus around the outside.
  - Medallion, 1996; 1 box (Box F.2)
    "Princeton University 250th Anniversary Nassau Hall 1746-1996" on front with picture of N. Hall.
  - Paperweight, 1996; 1 box (Box F.3)
    Lucite paperweight with invitation inside. Invitation for the "Joint Commemorative Session of the Legislature"
  - Picture, 1996; 1 box (Box F.1)
    Framed, with postcard and expanded picture of Alexander Hall.
  - Pin, 1996; 1 box (Box F.2)
    250th symbol.
  - Pin, 1996; 1 box (Box F.2)
    "ONE" with U. seal.
  - Pin, 1996; 1 box (Box F.2)
    Picture of Alexander Hall postcard.
  - Plaque, 1996 September 20; 1 box (Box F.2)
    Plaque with 1996 post card and 1946 Nassau Hall stamp. "Presented to Hal Shapiro, 9/20/96.
  - Umbrella, 1997; 1 box (Box Z.13)
    Black and orange. 250th celebration.
  - Water bottle, 1996; 1 box (Box F.3)
    Mineral Water."BCQH2O" 1 liter bottle.
  - Water bottle, 1996; 1 box (Box F.3)
    Mineral water bottle. "BCQ H20" 16 oz.
- Series 2: Awards, 1871 June 27-2005 April 7; 51 boxes
  This series contains Awards given by the University.
  - Award, 2005 April 7; 1 box (Box 9)
    AR.2005.045
    Presented to William H. Scheide '36 for generosity involved in establishing the "Scheide Professorship of Music History."
  - Award, 1981-1986; 1 box (Box 27)
    AR.1993.015
    Small bronze tiger statue. Presented to recognize the volunteers and staff of "A Campaign for Princeton, 1981-1986."
  - Certificate of Appreciation for Walter Phelps "Buzzer" Hall Upon Retirement, 1952; 1 box (Box 48)
    AR.1992.057
    Signed by the presidents of Princeton classes '1913 to '1952.
  - Bowl, Undated; 20 boxes (Box V, Box U, Box T)
    AR.1995.092
    Class of 1935 longest distance award. Every five years from 1935
    Class of 1935
  - Cup, 1910; 1 box (Box C.3)
    PUTAA Intercollegiate Relay race Feb 1910.
  - Cup, 1913; 1 box (Box C.1)
    EX4762
    Pewter. "Class 1903 Princeton University Decennial Reunion."
    Class of 1903
  - Goblet, 1914; 1 box (Box C.5)
    Class of 1911 3rd reunion, longest distance award.
    Class of 1911
  - National Historic Landmark dedication, Undated; 1 box (Box 22)
    U.S. Department of the Interior designation of The President's House as a National Historic Landmark.
  - Plaque, 1941-1942; 1 box (Box 20)
    AR.2004.037
    Princeton University Fund Graduate Council Award for the Largest Amount Raised, 1941-1942. Given to the Class of 1909
    Class of 1909
  - Plaque, 1996 September 18; 1 box (Box 20)
    Truman Scholarship Honor Institution award. Presented to Princeton University.
  - Plaque, Undated; 1 box (Box 36)
    AR.2009.040
    Reunion Long-Distance Prize. Wooden plaque given to member of Class of 1938 who traveled the furthest to reunions.
    Class of 1938
  - Silver Bowl, Undated; 20 boxes (Box V, Box U, Box T)
    "Class of 1935 Long Distance Award" Names of winners inscribed.
  - Silver cup, Undated; 20 boxes (Box V, Box U, Box T)
    "Presented to Robert Sylvanus Gardner the boy of 64 by his Fathers Class Mates" inscribed.
    Class of 1864
    Given by Margaret R. Wright
  - Silver cup, Undated; 20 boxes (Box V, Box U, Box T)
    "Presented by the Class of 1871 Princeton College to Henry Cummings Williams Class Boy born Oct. 4, 1873" inscribed.
    Class of 1871
    Given by M.F. Williams
  - Silver cup, 1933; 20 boxes (Box V, Box U, Box T)
    Three Handled Silver Cup. "In behalf of all who drank here from .." Inscribed on one side. Names on other two sides.
    Class of 1913
  - Silver cup, 1893; 20 boxes (Box V, Box U, Box T)
    AR.1998.015
    "Princeton 1893" and football inscribed on front.
  - Silver Cup, Undated; 20 boxes (Box V, Box U, Box T)
    "Class of 1915 Princeton Mid-Winter Reunion Long Distance Cup" on front. Names of Winners on back. One handle broken.
    Class of 1915
  - Silver Cup, 1874 July 15; 20 boxes (Box V, Box U, Box T)
    AR.1990.044
    "Presented by the Class of 77 of Princeton College to John S. Ely of the Freshman Crew In commemoration of their Victory at the College Regatta Saratoga, July 15 1874" inscribed.
    Class of 1877
  - Silver Cup, 1871 June 27; 20 boxes (Box V, Box U, Box T)
    "College of New Jersey Class of 1861 Presented to the Class Boy, James Wilde, Son of Edward L. Wilde. June 27, 1871" inscribed.
    Class of 1861
  - Silver Cup, Undated; 20 boxes (Box V, Box U, Box T)
    "The names affectionately inscribed on this cup are those of our classmates whose high achievements have added to the renown of Princeton University and brought distinction to the Class of 1915" inscribed as well as many names.
  - Silver Cup, 1908 June 23; 20 boxes (Box V, Box U, Box T)
    "To Russell W. Moore from his friends in the Princeton Club the 23rd of June 1908" inscribed.
    Class of 1883
  - Silver Cup, 1874 July 15; 20 boxes (Box V, Box U, Box T)
    "Presented by The Class of 77 of Princeton College to John S. Ely of the Freshman Crew In commemoration of their Victory at the College Regatta Saratoga July 15, 1874" inscribed.
  - Silver Cup, 1904; 20 boxes (Box V, Box U, Box T)
    "1882 William Stewart Tod for twenty years President of Princeton '84: his classmates upon this our twentieth anniversary by this token hold him in loving regard. 1904"
    Class of 1882
    More information on inside of cup.
  - Silver Greek style Cup, 1906; 20 boxes (Box V, Box U, Box T)
    "To the Princeton Quadrangle Club" on front. "In Memory of Frederick Henry Cossitt Dec. 11, 1883- July 1, 1906"
    Given by Herbert A. Davis, '49
  - Silver plate, Undated; 1 box (Box 36)
    Class of 1938. Distinguished Service Award.
  - Silver plated cup, 1884; 1 box (Box C.3)
    PCAA Caledonian Games 1884. 1st prize hammer throw.
    Class of 1885
    Gift of Mrs. J Russell Craig, 9/3/80
  - Silver plated cup, 1907; 20 boxes (Box V, Box U, Box T)
    "To John A. Campbell for thirty years president of the class of 1877, Princeton University.." inscribed.
  - Silver plated cup, 1930; 20 boxes (Box V, Box U, Box T)
    "Loving Cup Exercises June 15th Class of 1915 Princeton University Long Distance Trophy.." inscribed with name.
    John L. Mott won this award in 1925, Mason Olcott in 1930.
  - Silver Thermos, 1903-1933; 20 boxes (Box V, Box U, Box T)
    "Daffodils of Princeton 1903. 'And then my heart with pleasure fills and dances with the daffodils.' Wordsworth." names of winners inscribed.
    E4761
  - Silver tri-handled cup, 1949; 20 boxes (Box V, Box U, Box T)
    "Princeton 1899." "The class of 1899 at its 50th year reunion bequeaths this cup to the class of 1949 to have and to hold in trust for another fifty years and then, present it to the graduating class of 1999."
    Class of 1899
  - Silver trophy, Undated; 20 boxes (Box V, Box U, Box T)
    "Princeton Upper Class Club Scholarship Trophy." Nassau bell tower on top.
  - Trophy and pedestal, Undated; 1 box (Box 26)
    AR.2006.090
    Silver trophy. Presented to Princeton Wrestling Team. Wooden pedestal.
  - University seal, Undated; 1 box (Box C.7)
    Metal 6"x 9". Painted
  - University seal, circa 1921-1930; 1 box (Box C.7)
    Wooden with metal seal. Varnished.
    Anonymous gift in memory of Charles W Millard, Jr. '26. Received 10/25/89.
  - University seal, Undated; 1 box (Box C.7)
    Wooden with metal seal. Painted seal.
  - University seal, 1941; 1 box (Box C.7)
    Wooden with metal seal. "Grad Council Award, 1940-41 class of 1898 donors 100%."
    Class of 1898
  - University seal, Undated; 1 box (Box C.7)
    Mock leather with stamped seal.
  - University seal, Undated; 1 box (Box C.7)
    AR.1995 .034
    Wooden with metal seal. Large. One duplicate.
  - University seal, Undated; 1 box (Box C.3)
    EX4821/1
    Princeton gun club, Harvard match.
  - University seal, Undated; 1 box (Box C.3)
    EX4821/2
    Princeton gun club, Yale match.
- Series 3: Banners and Pennants, 1876-2008; 16 boxes; 22 items
  This series contains Banners and Pennants related to various University events and organizations.
  - Banner, circa 1879; 1 box (Box B.6)
    3'x3' cut cloth. "79"
    Class of 1879
  - Banner, 1897; 1 box (Box B.6)
    EX4568/4
    3'x4' "Princeton Yale May 7,1897 Winning Team\u2026" Black.
  - Banner, 1926; 1 item (Item Bag.1)
    "1926" with football and scores(P-10; Y-7; P-12; H-0) Orange. 5'x3'
  - Banner, 1922; 1 item (Item Bag.3)
    "Princeton 1922" 21"x46"
    Class of 1922
  - Banner, 1895; 1 box (Box B.6)
    "Princeton '95" 2'x2' Orange and black.
    Class of 1895
  - Banner, 1909; 1 item (Item Bag.2)
    "Princeton 1909" 4'x5' Black.
  - Banner, 1921; 1 item (Item Bag.2)
    "Princeton 1921" 4'x5' Black.
    Class of 1921
  - Banner, 1888; 1 item (Item Bag.2)
    "88" Orange flag. 6'x8'
    Class of 1888
  - Banner, Undated; 1 box (Box B.6)
    Black felt with fringed edges. 2'x2'. "Princeton"
  - Banner, Undated; 1 box (Box B.6)
    black with orange "Princeton". 18"x30"
  - Banner, circa 1899; 1 item (Item Bag.4)
    Large black and white banner with large orange bird and "99"
  - Banner, Undated; 1 item (Item Bag.2)
    8'X2.5' Black, "Princeton" in orange.
  - Banner, Undated; 1 box (Box B.6)
    15"'X15". Black with orange P
  - Banner, 1916; 1 item (Item Bag.3)
    AR.1996.093
    "1916" 5'X3'.
    Class of 1916
  - Banner, 1916; 1 item (Item Bag.3)
    "Princeton 1916" 6'X3'
  - Banner, 1951; 1 item (Item Bag.1)
    "Princeton 1+9+5+1=16" Orange, 3'X5'
  - Banner, 1922; 1 item (Item Bag.2)
    "1922" White. 5'X3'.
  - Banner, 1922; 1 box (Box B.6)
    Cut as Crest. Tiger and "22"
  - Banner, Undated; 1 box (Box B.7)
    1.5'X3'. Black w/Princeton and U. Seal.
  - Banner, 1949; 1 box (Box B.7)
    3'X2'. Black, "Big Three Champions, 47-48-49" with tiger and U Seal.
  - Banner, Undated; 1 item (Item Bag.1)
    AR.1997.089
    Black banner with "Princeton 1938" in orange.
  - Banner, 1915; 1 item (Item Bag.5)
    AR.2000.056
    33x69. Felt, black with orange lettering.
  - Banner, 1919; 1 item (Item Bag.5)
    AR.2000.057
    Class of 1919
  - Banner, 1935; 1 item (Item Bag.6)
    AR.2000.058
    23x45. Felt, black with colored footballs representing opponents with game scores.
  - Banner, 1928; 1 item (Item Bag.6)
    AR.2000.089
    32x72. Felt, black with orange lettering.
    Class of 1928
  - Banner, 1904; 1 item (Item Bag.7)
    AR.2001.057
    6ft.x10ft. Orange (cotton?) with "1904" in black.
    Class of 1904
  - Banner, Undated; 1 box (Box 6)
    AR.2006.005
    Class of 1970. White field featuring locust with Princeton Shield on its back.
    Class of 1970
  - Banner, Undated; 1 box (Box 10)
    AR.2005.035
    Orange banner with black "P."
  - Banner, Undated; 1 item (Item Bag.9)
    "1907." Black banner with orange lettering.
    Class of 1907
  - Banner, 2000 December 13; 1 item (Item Bag.10)
    AR.2004.012
    "The Centennial of the Graduate School." Large white banner.
  - Banner, Undated; 1 item (Item Bag.11)
    "The Centennial of the Graduate College." Large white banner.
  - Black banner, Undated; 1 box (Box B.9)
    17" x 9" "Princeton" and seal in orange. Orange border.
  - Cloth, Undated; 1 box (Box B.9)
    Red oriental run with U seal. 9"x6"
  - Cloth, 1914; 1 box (Box B.6)
    Orange, rectangular, 7.5"*21"; 35th reunion of the class of 1879; List of US Presidents, from Washington to Wilson.
  - Cloth, Undated; 1 box (Box 24)
    AR.2004.007
    Off-white cloth with orange lettering "Princeton" and tiger leaning on a "P."
  - Cut cloth, Undated; 1 box (Box B.9)
    Bird on orange felt. 6"x9" Class year symbol.
  - Cut cloth, Undated; 1 box (Box B.9)
    Orange felt. "Old Nassau" verse written on it.
  - Embroidered cloth, Undated; 1 box (Box B.9)
    white with orange U seal and "P".
  - Flag, Undated; 1 box (Box B.9)
    Orange and black with handle.
  - Flag, Undated; 1 box (Box B.7)
    Orange and black bars. 2'X1.5'.
  - Flag, Undated; 1 box (Box B.7)
    Orange. Tiger with firecracker. 1746-1896. Celebrating 150th.
  - Flag, Undated; 1 box (Box B.7)
    Flag on wooden stick. Black and orange. 21"x17."
  - Moon Flag, 1969; 1 item (Item 2)
    Flag in frame. White with orange and black seal. Went to moon. "To Bud with best wishes Charles Conrad P'53 14-24 Nov '69".
  - Moon Flag, 1969; 1 box (Box 48)
    AR.2006.027
    White with orange and black seal. Flag that went to the moon, signed by Charles Conrad. Housed with photocopies of 1970 article and 1999 Conrad obituary.
  - Flag, 2008; 1 box (Box B.9)
    AR.2008.108
    White with Princeton shield and black lettering "Princeton University." Autographed by Transformers director Michael Bay and actors Shia LaBeouf, Megan Fox and Ramon Rodriguez.
  - Flag, Undated; 1 box (Box 6)
    White flag with Princeton Shield. "Princeton University" in black lettering.
  - Flag, 1959; 1 box (Box 28)
    American flag with 49 stars. Flew over Blair Arch.
  - Football banner, 1947-1949; 1 box (Box B.18)
    Big three champions: Princeton, Harvard, Yale. 1947, '48, '49. Tiger, Princeton shield and scores.
  - Hanging rug, Undated; 1 box (Box B.6)
    Princeton pennant with tiger and seal on Turkish rug-type background. 3'x18"
  - Large black banner, 2003 April 9; 1 box (Box B.18)
    AR.2002.032
    Princeton class of 1945, mini reunion - Washington DC.
    Class of 1945
  - Large white banner, Undated; 1 box (Box B.18)
    AR.2002.031
    Princeton Shield with picture of the Graduate School on it.
  - Maroon and white felt banner, 1980; 1 box (Box B.19)
    AR.2003.030
    Princeton University Chamber Chorus, Glee Club 1980.
  - Orange flag, Undated; 1 box (Box B.19)
    AR.2003.001
    with a black P on a stick.
  - Orange Ribbon, 1886; 1 box (Box B.7)
    with "Class '86" in black.
    Class of 1886
  - Painting, Undated; 1 box (Box B.6)
    U seal with woman's face. By F. Earl Christy. 2'x2'
  - Painting on cloth., Undated; 1 item (Item Bag.2)
    Tiger and cub. 2'x4'
  - Paper flags, Undated; 1 box (Box 24)
    AR.2008.125
    Orange paper flags with black lettering "Princeton."
  - Pendant, Undated; 1 box (Box B.7)
    "87" black and orange.
    Class of 1887
  - Pennant, 1891; 1 box (Box B.10)
    '91. Black.
    Class of 1891
  - Pennant, 1901; 1 box (Box B.10)
    1901 Black.
    Class of 1901
  - Pennant, 1948; 1 box (Box B.10)
    "'48 Anzacs" Orange.
    Class of 1948
  - Pennant, 1967; 1 box (Box B.10)
    "67" Orange. 1967?
    Class of 1967
  - Pennant, Undated; 1 box (Box B.6)
    "Princeton" with tiger head. Black.
  - Pennant, Undated; 1 box (Box B.6)
    "Princeton" with tiger head. Black and orange.
  - Pennant, Undated; 1 box (Box B.6)
    "Princeton" with tiger head and football players' names.
  - Pennant, Undated; 1 box (Box B.6)
    "Princeton" with buttons and pins attached.
  - Pennant, Undated; 1 box (Box B.6)
    "Princeton" orange and black. 3'x2'.
  - Pennant, Undated; 1 box (Box B.6)
    Black on one side, orange on other. Rope border. Black "P" on orange pennant on black background. "CEW" on Orange background.
  - Pennant, circa 1879; 1 box (Box B.6)
    Orange pennant with "79" on one side, "P" on other.
  - Pennant, 1876; 1 box (Box B.10)
    '76.
    Class of 1876
  - Pennant, Undated; 1 box (Box B.7)
    Black. Princeton, with U. Seal.
  - Pennant, Undated; 1 item (Item 3)
    Black and Orange with "Princeton" embroidered. Framed.
  - Pennant, Undated; 1 box (Box B.7)
    Black and orange with "Princeton."
  - Pennant, Undated; 1 box (Box B.7)
  - Pennant, circa 1976; 1 box (Box B.7)
    "76."
    Class of 1976
  - Picture, circa 1900; 1 box (Box B.6)
    Picture painted on canvas. Gibson girl holding Princeton pennant and Princeton football player.
  - Princeton Shield, Undated; 1 box (Box B.19)
    in a black frame.
  - Ribbon, Undated; 1 box (Box B.7)
    Orange and Black.
  - Rug, Undated; 1 box (Box B.9)
    Painted tiger skin rug on felt. 12"x9"
  - Scroll painting, Undated; 1 box (Box B.6)
    Tigers and Cheetahs.
  - Scroll painting, Undated; 1 box (Box B.6)
    Tiger.
  - Silk cloth, Undated; 1 box (Box B.13)
    Black with tigers, etc. Class of 1956.
    Class of 1956
  - Small flag, Undated; 1 box (Box 24)
    Class of 1970. White flag. Locuust with Princeton Shield on its back. With picture of creator.
  - Strip banner, 1887; 1 box (Box B.10)
    "87" 18" Orange.
  - Strip banner, Undated; 1 box (Box B.7)
    Orange and black strips, white border. 2'x1'
  - Table cloth, Undated; 1 item (Item Bag.3)
    (friendship bridge cloth). Signatures embroidered with multi-colored thread.
    Owned by Joseph Maull Carey '16. Given by Charles and Margaret Carey.
  - Table cloth, 1896; 1 item (Item Bag.3)
    Signatures embroidered in orange and black thread.
    Class of 1896
    Given by Mrs. Graham Hunter in 1952.
  - Tapestry, circa 1904; 1 box (Box B-)
    3'X5'. Black with U-seal, 1904 Princeton.
  - University seal, Undated; 1 box (Box C.7)
    AR.1996.051
    wooden with metal emblem.
  - White cloth with seal, 1969; 1 box (Box B.9)
    One of five taken to moon by Charles Conrad '53 in 1969.
  - White cloth with seal, 1969; 1 box (Box B.6)
    One of five that were took to moon by Charles Conrad '53 in 1969.
- Series 4: Clothing, 1878-2010; 52 boxes
  The clothing group includes handkerchiefs, hatbands, and neckties.
  - 25th Reunion silk scarf, 1995; 1 box (Box B.20)
    AR.2001.065
    Class of 1970.
  - 50th reunion sash, Undated; 1 box (Box B.20)
    AR.2001.015
    Orange with black trim and gold writing.
  - Anniversary Campaign T-shirt, Undated; 1 box (Box B.20)
    Orange with white "ONE" on the front.
  - Anniversary Campaign T-shirt, Undated; 1 box (Box B.20)
    Black with Orange "ONE" on front.
  - Armband, Undated; 1 box (Box B.4)
    Orange 22.
  - Armband?, Undated; 1 box (Box B.10)
    "P" Orange.
  - Bag, 1990; 1 box (Box B.16)
    AR.2002.040
    White and Orange. Class of 1970. 20th reunion. Cicada pattern.
  - Bag, Undated; 1 box (Box B.20)
    AR.2000.130
    White and black bag with orange striped handles. Class of 1970 Cicada and Princeton shield pattern.
  - Bandana, 1990; 1 box (Box B.16)
    Class of 1970. 20th reunion. In locusts parentis. Cicada pattern.
  - Baseball cap, 1928; 1 box (Box B.14)
    AR.1998.018
  - Beer Jacket, Undated; 1 box (Box B.16)
    1929.
    Class of 1929
  - Beer Jacket, 1995; 1 box (Box B.16)
    1970's 25th. Cicada pattern.
  - Belt, Undated; 1 box (Box B.11)
    Black leather with tiger head buckle.
  - Belt, Undated; 1 box (Box B.11)
    Orange and black ribbon with snake buckle.
  - Belt, Undated; 1 box (Box 45)
    AR.2009.089
    Orange, black and white belt with tiger stripe pattern.
  - Black bag, Undated; 1 box (Box B.10)
    Orange lined sack with draw string.
  - Black bag, Undated; 1 box (Box B.10)
    Orange lined purse.
  - Black bag, 1885; 1 box (Box B.10)
    Orange lined purse. With bow and embroidery. "Jennis 7-2-85"
  - Black T-shirt, Undated; 1 box (Box B.20)
    with orange P on front
  - Black T-shirt, Undated; 1 box (Box B.20)
    with orange triangular Princeton shield on front.
  - Bow tie, Undated; 1 box (Box B.11)
    Black with orange 1927.
    Class of 1927
  - Cap, Undated; 1 box (Box B.20)
    AR.2003.082
    Freshman Dink
  - Class Jacket, Undated; 1 box (Box B.8)
    Black and orange, "20"
    Class of 1920
  - Class Jacket, Undated; 1 box (Box B.8)
    White denim, "49er" on back.
    Class of 1949
  - Class sweater, Undated; 1 box (Box B.20)
  - Cloth, 1939; 1 box (Box B.6)
    '39 emblems stitched into piece of cloth.
  - Cloth, Undated; 1 box (Box B.10)
    17" x 12" with black "P" on orange background.
  - Cloth, Undated; 1 box (Box B.7)
    Black and orange stripes.
  - Coaster, Undated; 1 box (Box B.9)
    Linen, white and round; two tigers along the circumference in pink, gold, white and black; "79" in between in pink.
  - Coveralls, Undated; 1 box (Box 15)
    AR.2006.086
    Off-white front. Black and orange sleeves and back.
  - Cummerbund?, Undated; 1 box (Box B.10)
    Cumberband? "19 P 13" Orange. 5'
  - Doctoral hood, Undated; 1 box (Box B.7)
    Black and orange.
  - Doctoral hood, Undated; 1 box (Box B.7)
  - Fabric, Undated; 1 box (Box 16)
    Binder of "Princeton University Reunion Fabrics." Individually labeled fabric patches. Includes "Collected Samples of Reunion Jackets, Neckties, Patches, Etcetera"
    AR.2003.091
    Assembled by Van Zandt Williams, Jr. '65 and the Alumni Council Committee on Princetoniana
  - Gray Hat, Undated; 1 box (Box B.20)
    with orange and black P on front and "The Anniversary Campaign for Princeton" on back.
  - Gray T-shirt, Undated; 1 box (Box B.20)